<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>BeAPI Blog</title>
        <link>https://beapijs.github.io/BeAPI/blog</link>
        <description>BeAPI Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome]]></title>
            <link>https://beapijs.github.io/BeAPI/blog/welcome</link>
            <guid>welcome</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[First off, welcome to BeAPI's first release 🎉]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>First off, welcome to BeAPI's first release 🎉
Thank you for sticking with us and helping us
contemplate ideas for this package. It sure
has been an intriguing journey up to this point.</p><p><img loading="lazy" alt="BeAPI Logo" src="/BeAPI/assets/images/beapi-4603cf2680132a588e928408bdbe7851.png" width="1280" height="640"></p><p>Now with that aside...</p><p>It's 3:45 in the morning, and I just finished
writing all the docs out for this bad boy
<em>after procrastinating and playing Walkabout Mini Golf with some friends.</em></p><p>Let me say; Writing documentation truly makes
you contemplate life: "why am I here?",
"How did I get here?", "Can I go to bed now?".
BUT NO... I feel like a freaking world war translator
decrypting massive files of gibberish written by my
peers with no help.</p><p>I was ultimately planning on removing the blogs page from
this website. My mindset at the time was something along the
lines of: "You've got me <!-- -->*<!-- -->*<!-- -->*<!-- -->*<!-- -->*<!-- -->*<!-- --> up if you think I am going to
write more words!"</p><p>BUT After briefly reconsidering, I figured maybe posting here
would be fun, thus my resolve to write this.</p><p>Anyways, even though BeAPI is released to the public fully now,
I do want to warn, we are going to violate semver a bit. We
made some changes to the beta branch we meant to push to production,
but we got ahead of ourselves accidentally and made a release.</p><p>I'll probably end up just throwing changes like that in a migration
guide or something when I decide to add version management to the docs.</p><p>_</p><p>I suppose that is all I have for this first post. I apologize if it's
a bit bland, but you should probably cut me some slack; It's now 4:00 in
the morning, and my brain is deep-fried.</p><p>Once again, thank you very much all for the continued
support we love ya ❤️ <em>no homo... or maybe not?</em> 😳</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>welcome</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>